[Theme song]
[Lagu tema]
[dark music]
[musik gelap]
[Bird chirping]
[Kicau burung]
[Heavy sound effect]
[Efek suara berat]
(Gwangshin) You know singer Bang Hyun-min, right?
(Gwangshin) Anda kenal penyanyi Bang Hyun-min, kan?
Ah, why, in the old days There was a singer who was popular.
Ah, kenapa, di masa lalu Ada seorang penyanyi yang populer.
From a group called Axtage
Dari grup bernama Axtage
That Bang Hyun-min I created an entertainment company, right?
Bang Hyun-min itu Saya membuat perusahaan hiburan, bukan?
Wow, but
Wah tapi
I got it from here and there They say the investment amount is quite large.
Saya mendapatkannya dari sana-sini Mereka bilang jumlah investasinya cukup besar.
No, well, a celebrity. It's like creating an entertainment company.
Bukan, yah, seorang selebriti. Ini seperti mendirikan perusahaan hiburan.
It's not surprising
Itu tidak mengherankan
Entertainment company stock prices in the stock market these days
Harga saham perusahaan hiburan di pasar saham hari ini
You all know that we are hitting the closing price, right?
Anda semua tahu bahwa kami sedang mencapai harga penutupan, bukan?
huh? I don't know?
Hah? Aku tidak tahu?
Oh, Miss Jeong, you know.
Oh, Nona Jeong, Anda tahu.
No, no matter what Even if it’s a shitty company
Tidak, tidak peduli apapun yang terjadi Meskipun itu perusahaan yang buruk
Once you do a backdoor listing or whatever,
Setelah Anda melakukan pencatatan pintu belakang atau apa pun,
It's a bunch of bullshit, it's crazy.
Itu omong kosong, gila.
But there's a problem with this
Tapi ada masalah dengan ini
Sales are slow?
Penjualan lambat?
So Bang Hyun-min Are you looking for a place to increase sales?
Jadi Bang Hyun Min Apakah Anda mencari tempat untuk meningkatkan penjualan?
Are you planning to go public?
Apakah Anda berencana untuk go public?
(Gwangshin) [Snaps fingers] That’s right.
(Gwangshin) [Menjentikkan jari] Benar.
So we First, go to Hyunmin Bang’s subsidiary.
Jadi kita Pertama, pergi ke anak perusahaan Hyunmin Bang.
If it increases sales, it's a blessing.
Kalau bisa meningkatkan penjualan, itu berkah.
And we hire celebrities from entertainment companies.
Dan kami mempekerjakan selebriti dari perusahaan hiburan.
It can also be used as a promotional model.
Ini juga dapat digunakan sebagai model promosi.
Oh!
Oh!
(Sangcheon) I also got investment money Celebrities can also be used as promotional models.
(Sangcheon) Saya juga mendapat uang investasi Selebriti juga bisa dijadikan model promosi.
Kill two birds with one stone
Bunuh dua burung dengan satu batu
Ah, then Bang Hyun-min
Ah, lalu Bang Hyun-min
[Laughing] Our eh, eh, angel!
[Tertawa] Eh, eh, malaikat kami!
[Everyone laughs]
[Semua orang tertawa]
(Soram) That person, Bang Hyunmin
(Soram) Orang itu, Bang Hyunmin
Stay away
Menjauhlah
[disapproving sound] (Gwangshin) Ah, Miss Jeong-eun Why are you suddenly hitting the candle?
[suara tidak setuju] (Gwangshin) Ah, Nona Jeong-eun Mengapa Anda tiba-tiba memukul lilinnya?
(Soram) You know
(Soram) Anda tahu
I once told a member of the National Assembly I came here to lobby
Saya pernah bercerita kepada seorang anggota Majelis Nasional Saya datang ke sini untuk melobi
(Sangcheon) Um, Secretary Jeong Are you saying you know Bang Hyun-min well?
(Sangcheon) Um, Sekretaris Jeong Maksudmu kamu kenal baik Bang Hyun-min?
(Soram) I know
(Soram) Saya tahu
Everywhere I looked, I rejected him because he was a lousy person.
Ke mana pun saya memandang, saya menolaknya karena dia orang yang buruk.
[Youngjin’s laughter]
[Tawa Youngjin]
(Youngjin) Mr. Lee, hey, what, aren’t we cool?
(Youngjin) Tuan Lee, hei, apa, keren kan?
[Sound of pain] [Interesting music]
[Suara kesakitan] [Musik yang menarik]
(Sangcheon) What’s wrong with us? You bastard
(Sangcheon) Ada apa dengan kita? Kamu bajingan
너는 아직도 그, 스트리트 사기꾼 마인드야, 이 새끼야
너는 아직도 그, 스트리트 사기꾼 마인드야, 이 새끼야
너 빨리 비즈니스 마인드로 체인지해, 이 새끼야, 씨
너 빨리 비즈니스 마인드로 체인지해, 이 새끼야, 씨
[상천의 못마땅한 소리]
[상천의 못마땅한 소리]
그래서? When can I see it?
bagus? Kapan saya bisa melihatnya?
(Fanatical) Yes, that's why I
(Fanatis) Ya, itu sebabnya saya
We've already decided to meet at the hotel.
Kami sudah memutuskan untuk bertemu di hotel.
(Hyunmin) Did you see me? What I do
(Hyunmin) Apakah kamu melihatku? Apa yang saya lakukan
Are you on a diet?
Apakah Anda sedang diet?
(Woman 1) Yes, I am doing it.
(Wanita 1) Ya, saya melakukannya.
(Hyunmin) But why is it like this?
(Hyunmin) Tapi kenapa jadi seperti ini?
(Woman 1) [Laughing] We need to do more.
(Wanita 1) [Tertawa] Kita perlu berbuat lebih banyak.
(Hyunmin) You have chubby cheeks, Mr.
(Hyunmin) Pipimu tembem, Tn.
- (Hyunmin) Work hard - (Woman 1) Yes
- (Hyunmin) Bekerja keras - (Wanita 1) Ya
(Sangcheon) It’s Jeomma. [Sangcheon’s laughter]
(Sangcheon) Ini Jeomma. [Tawa Sangcheon]
Hello! This is Noh Sang-cheon.
Halo! Ini Noh Sang Cheon.
(Hyunmin) This is Bang Hyunmin, CEO of BHM Entertainment.
(Hyunmin) Ini Bang Hyunmin, CEO BHM Entertainment.
[Sangcheon’s response] My face is my business card
[Respon Sangcheon] Wajahku adalah kartu namaku
[Women and Hyunmin’s laughter]
[Tawa wanita dan Hyunmin]
[Laugh together]
[Tertawa bersama]
(Fantastic) Oh, yes, of course, I know.
(Fantastis) Oh ya, tentu saja saya tahu.
(Hyunmin) Ah, these guys Our company really likes it
(Hyunmin) Ah, orang-orang ini Perusahaan kami sangat menyukainya
our aces
kartu as kami
Guys, I have to say hello.
Teman-teman, aku harus menyapa.
(Woman 2) Hello, my name is Chomi.
(Wanita 2) Halo, nama saya Chomi.
(Woman 1) I’m Seoju.
(Wanita 1) Saya Seoju.
(Women) Please take care of me
(Wanita) Tolong jaga aku
(Hyunmin) Yes, yes, ayu, it’s pretty.
(Hyunmin) Ya, ya, ayu, cantik sekali.
you guys go there I'm eating something delicious
kalian pergi ke sana Aku sedang makan sesuatu yang enak
[Women's excited sounds] Because we have to talk about business.
[Suara gembira wanita] Karena kita harus membicarakan bisnis.
Uh, order something expensive.
Uh, pesan sesuatu yang mahal.
(Women) Thank you
(Wanita) Terima kasih
(Hyunmin) Oh, there you go, Seoju.
(Hyunmin) Oh, ini dia, Seoju.
- (Woman 1) Yes? - (Hyunmin) Adjust it.
- (Wanita 1) Ya? - (Hyunmin) Sesuaikan.
- (Woman 1) [Laughing] Yes. - (Hyunmin) It’s full, now.
- (Wanita 1) [Tertawa] Ya. - (Hyunmin) Sekarang sudah penuh.
- (Woman 1) Yes - (Hyeonmin) Oh
- (Wanita 1) Ya - (Hyeonmin) Oh
(Hyunmin) Okay, now you’re saying that. Let's talk business.
(Hyunmin) Oke, sekarang kamu mengatakan itu. Mari kita bicara bisnis.
(Sangcheon) Oh, so this is
(Sangcheon) Oh, jadi ini
Wow, amazing sales It's a business that happens
Wah, penjualannya luar biasa Ini adalah bisnis yang terjadi
Uh, the CEO said the initial investment and If you just promise to provide promotional support...
Eh, CEO bilang investasi awal dan Jika Anda hanya berjanji untuk memberikan dukungan promosi...
Oh, that’s right, one year’s sales are Approximately how much do you expect?
Oh iya, penjualannya satu tahun Kira-kira berapa yang Anda harapkan?
(Sangcheon) Oh, so From our strategic planning team
(Sangcheon) Oh, jadi Dari tim perencanaan strategis kami
very conservatively Annual sales target is approximately KRW 10 billion
dengan sangat konservatif Target penjualan tahunan sekitar KRW 10 miliar
(Hyunmin) 10 billion...
(Hyunmin) 10 miliar...
Well, this isn’t bad, right?
Ya, ini tidak buruk, bukan?
(Sangcheon) Is that right? Besides that Now, in the case of margins,
(Sangcheon) Benarkah? Selain itu Sekarang, dalam hal margin,
of the annual sales About 45% to 50%...
dari penjualan tahunan Sekitar 45% hingga 50%...
Wow, what is margin, is it important?
Wah, apa itu margin, pentingkah?
(Hyeonmin) This is Representative Kim Seong-dae. This is the person who connected me, so I have to do it no matter what.
(Hyeonmin) Ini Perwakilan Kim Seong-dae. Inilah orang yang menghubungkan saya, jadi saya harus melakukannya apa pun yang terjadi.
Only business content on paper Please summarize briefly.
Hanya konten bisnis di atas kertas Silakan rangkum secara singkat.
(Sangcheon) Paper?
(Sangcheon) Kertas?
Yes, okay?
Ya oke?
(Sangcheon) [Laughing] Okay
(Sangcheon) [Tertawa] Oke
[Laugh together]
[Tertawa bersama]
(Youngjin) No, well, like that They say it’s easy to decide to invest?
(Youngjin) Tidak, seperti itu Katanya mudah memutuskan berinvestasi?
Is there any money left? uh? [Youngjin’s laughter]
Apakah masih ada uang tersisa? eh? [Tawa Youngjin]
(Sangcheon) [snaps fingers] Bingo That's it
(Sangcheon) [menjentikkan jari] Bingo Itu saja
It's not your money.
Itu bukan uangmu.
I received investments from all over the place. There is no suitable investment destination, huh?
Saya menerima investasi dari berbagai tempat. Belum ada tujuan investasi yang cocok ya?
We need to get listed as an entertainment company right away.
Kami harus segera terdaftar sebagai perusahaan hiburan.
Just increase sales It's okay to be anything
Tingkatkan saja penjualannya Tidak apa-apa menjadi apa pun
Besides, our business is good.
Selain itu, bisnis kami bagus.
Above all, you have a big belly.
Yang terpenting, Anda memiliki perut yang besar.
[Youngjin and Sangcheon’s laughter] (Fanatical) Ah, the congressman is just You just introduced me.
[Tawa Youngjin dan Sangcheon] (Fanatis) Ah, anggota kongres itu adil Anda baru saja memperkenalkan saya.
(Sangcheon) Oh, that’s right, introduction
(Sangcheon) Oh, benar, perkenalan
[Laughing] Oh, Rep. Kim You just introduced me.
[Tertawa] Oh, Perwakilan Kim Anda baru saja memperkenalkan saya.
Ah, I run the business.
Ah, saya menjalankan bisnis.
Oh, just in case If something happens
Oh, untuk berjaga-jaga Jika sesuatu terjadi
To Rep. Kim There's no harm
Kepada Rep.Kim Tidak ada salahnya
[Laughter of fanaticism] don't worry about that
[Tertawa fanatisme] jangan khawatir tentang itu
Now that we have secured the investment [Youngjin’s response]
Sekarang kami telah mengamankan investasinya [Respon Youngjin]
[Interesting music] Let’s give it a try in earnest!
[Musik yang menarik] Mari kita mencobanya dengan sungguh-sungguh!
[Laugh together]
[Tertawa bersama]
[Sangcheon and Yeongjin’s excited exclamation]
[Seruan gembira Sangcheon dan Yeongjin]
(Sangcheon) ♪ How did you live ♪ [Youngjin’s cheers]
(Sangcheon) ♪ Bagaimana caramu hidup ♪ [sorakan Youngjin]
♪ Don’t ask ♪
♪ Jangan tanya ♪
[People cheering]
[Orang-orang bersorak]
(Narrator Model) Yes, everyone. Nice to meet you
(Model Narator) Ya, semuanya. Senang bertemu denganmu
Everyone, today is now free. Celebrating 100,000 subscribers
Semuanya, hari ini bebas. Merayakan 100.000 pelanggan
Big event, super special event It's progressing, thank you!
Acara besar, acara super spesial Ini mengalami kemajuan, terima kasih!
Yes, today is now free.
Ya, hari ini sekarang gratis.
New events, special offers In progress
Acara baru, penawaran khusus Sedang berlangsung
Many people came and received many free gifts...
Banyak orang datang dan menerima banyak hadiah gratis...
- (Woman 3) Sister, you’re so pretty. - (Woman 4) Wow, I love you [Celebrity laughter]
- (Wanita 3) Kakak, kamu cantik sekali. - (Wanita 4) Wah, aku cinta kamu [Tawa selebriti]
[Excited sounds of Woman 3 and Woman 4]
[Suara heboh Wanita 3 dan Wanita 4]
(Celebrity) See you next time
(Selebriti) Sampai jumpa lagi
- (Celebrity) What is your name? - (Woman 5) Dain.
- (Selebriti) Siapa namamu? - (Wanita 5) Dain.
[People are noisy] (Celebrity) Dain
[Orang-orang berisik] (Selebriti) Dain
(Hyunmin) Wow, that’s awesome, CEO Noh?
(Hyunmin) Wow, luar biasa, CEO Noh?
[Sangcheon’s light smile]
[Senyum ringan Sangcheon]
(Sangcheon) This is all from our room representative. Thanks to the investment
(Sangcheon) Ini semua dari perwakilan kamar kami. Berkat investasinya
This is all the CEO’s money.
Ini semua adalah uang CEO.
[Hyeonmin and Sangcheon’s laughter]
[Tawa Hyeonmin dan Sangcheon]
(Hyunmin) Please just increase sales.
(Hyunmin) Tolong tingkatkan saja penjualannya.
(Sangcheon) Of course, of course.
(Sangcheon) Tentu saja.
No matter what anyone says, we are BHM Entertainment’s Isn't it a subsidiary?
Tidak peduli apa kata orang, kami adalah milik BHM Entertainment Bukankah itu anak perusahaan?
[Sangcheon’s laughter] (Hyunmin) Hey, what is the subsidiary?
[Tawa Sangcheon] (Hyunmin) Hei, anak perusahaannya apa?
family
keluarga
family, family
keluarga, keluarga
[Hyeonmin and Sangcheon’s laughter]
[Tawa Hyeonmin dan Sangcheon]
(Sangcheon) Point [Hyeonmin’s laughter]
(Sangcheon) Poin [Tawa Hyeonmin]
[Meaningful music]
[Musik yang bermakna]
[Hyeonmin’s satisfied voice]
[Suara puas Hyeonmin]
(Soram) The business here will be settled soon.
(Soram) Urusan di sini akan segera diselesaikan.
When will you contact me, Rep.?
Kapan Anda akan menghubungi saya, Rep.?
No, it's okay
Tidak, tidak apa-apa
Rep. send me your schedule.
Rep. kirimkan saya jadwal Anda.
I'll check and contact you.
Saya akan memeriksa dan menghubungi Anda.
If you want to send it, send it
Jika Anda ingin mengirimkannya, kirimkan saja
Where does it work, it doesn't work!
Di mana cara kerjanya, tidak berhasil!
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Suara pengoperasian ponsel]
[sigh]
[menghela nafas]
Who are you calling? Are you that excited?
Siapa yang kamu telepon? Apakah kamu begitu bersemangat?
Not like Jeong So-ram
Tidak seperti Jeong So-ram
I don't know anything
Saya tidak tahu apa-apa
(Sangcheon) Now slowly Isn’t it time to decide?
(Sangcheon) Sekarang pelan-pelan Bukankah ini saatnya untuk memutuskan?
[Interesting music]
[Musik yang menarik]
your future
masa depanmu
[Blows out air]
[Menghembuskan udara]
[Knocking sound]
[Suara ketukan]
[Sound of pain] [The door clicks open]
[Suara kesakitan] [Pintunya terbuka]
Mr...
Tuan...
[Vocal cords blow air]
[Pita suara mengembuskan udara]
(Secretary) Noh Sang-cheon’s business It seems like things are going well.
(Sekretaris) Bisnis Noh Sang-cheon Sepertinya semuanya berjalan baik.
When is the VIP reception?
Kapan resepsi VIPnya?
(Secretary) After completing overseas tour It's two months later when you come back.
(Sekretaris) Setelah menyelesaikan tur ke luar negeri Dua bulan kemudian Anda kembali.
(Vocal cords) Oh, just in time You can contact Jeong So-ram.
(Pita suara) Oh, tepat pada waktunya Anda bisa menghubungi Jeong So Ram.
(Secretary) I write, even if I don’t
(Sekretaris) Saya menulis, meskipun tidak
I keep getting calls from Senior Jeong.
Saya terus menerima telepon dari Senior Jeong.
Why?
Mengapa?
I want to talk to the congressman.
Saya ingin berbicara dengan anggota kongres.
Oh, there's no benefit in contacting you often.
Oh, tidak ada gunanya sering menghubungimu.
Now on Noh Sang-cheon’s side How many times do I tell you to stick close
Sekarang di pihak Noh Sang-cheon Berapa kali aku menyuruhmu untuk tetap dekat
Okay, go out.
Oke, keluar.
[sigh] [The door slams shut]
[menghela nafas] [Pintu dibanting hingga tertutup]
Selling more than you think Good ability, Noh Sang-cheon
Menjual lebih dari yang Anda kira Kemampuan bagus, Noh Sang-cheon
[Youngjin’s laughter]
[Tawa Youngjin]
[Youngjin’s cheers] [Counter operating sound]
[sorakan Youngjin] [Suara operasi counter]
(Youngjin) Hey, this is...
(Youngjin) Hei, ini...
I'm so happy
Saya sangat senang
[The door clicks open] (Sangcheon) Child...
[Pintunya terbuka] (Sangcheon) Anak...
[Gwangshin’s encouraging sound]
[Suara penyemangat Gwangshin]
(fanaticism) Wow!
(fanatisme) Wow!
Hey, how much is this? No boss?
Hei, berapa harganya? Tidak bos?
(Youngjin) Oh, this is it I'll pay off all my debt, huh?
(Youngjin) Oh, ini dia Aku akan melunasi semua hutangku ya?
I did that, right? Everyone just trust me
Saya melakukan itu, kan? Semua orang percaya saja padaku
(Soram) If you just get to this box, This month's settlement is complete.
(Soram) Jika kamu baru saja sampai ke kotak ini, Penyelesaian bulan ini selesai.
(Sangcheon) Let me see for a moment.
(Sangcheon) Coba saya lihat sebentar.
[Sangcheon snaps his fingers] [High Heaven's Whistle]
[Sangcheon menjentikkan jarinya] [Peluit Surga Tinggi]
[Counter operating sound]
[Suara operasi counter]
(Sangcheon) Take care of yourself.
(Sangcheon) Jaga dirimu baik-baik.
(Youngjin) Yes
(Youngjin) Ya
[Phone rings]
[Telepon berdering]
Hello?
Halo?
Where?
Di mana?
[The phone rings repeatedly]
[Telepon berdering berulang kali]
A broadcasting station?
Stasiun penyiaran?
(Anchor 1 on TV) Recently, I received a free phone call. Nowfree, which caused a craze
(Anchor 1 di TV) Baru-baru ini, saya menerima panggilan telepon gratis. Sekarang gratis, yang menyebabkan kegilaan
Due to frequent communication failures I'm in trouble
Karena seringnya terjadi kegagalan komunikasi aku dalam masalah
Mr. Noh [dark music]
Pak Noh [musik gelap]
(Anchor 1 on TV) Among some users,
(Anchor 1 di TV) Di antara beberapa pengguna,
Walkie-talkie, not a phone Some say it was bought
Walkie-talkie, bukan telepon Ada yang bilang itu dibeli
Accordingly, our reporters
Oleh karena itu, wartawan kami
Nowfree's Fake Phone We investigated suspicions of fraud.
Telepon Palsu Nowfree Kami menyelidiki dugaan penipuan.
[Sangcheon’s Sigh]
[Desahan Sangcheon]
(Sangcheon) It exploded earlier than expected
(Sangcheon) Itu meledak lebih awal dari yang diperkirakan
(Gwangshin) Mr. Noh What do we do now? [Youngjin’s anxious breathing]
(Gwangshin) Tuan Noh Apa yang kita lakukan sekarang? [Napas cemas Youngjin]
(Youngjin) Even the money I have now Should I lift it and jump?
(Youngjin) Bahkan uang yang saya miliki sekarang Haruskah aku mengangkatnya dan melompat?
This is still enough You can live comfortably for several years.
Ini masih cukup Anda dapat hidup nyaman selama beberapa tahun.
(Sangcheon) Be quiet so I can think about it.
(Sangcheon) Diamlah agar aku bisa memikirkannya.
Shut up, even just for one minute! Mr.
Diam, meski hanya satu menit! Tuan.
(Gwangshin) Boy, this is the situation. How can you be quiet!
(Gwangshin) Wah, beginilah situasinya. Bagaimana kamu bisa diam!
[Angry breathing]
[Nafas marah]
[Sound of pain]
[Suara kesakitan]
[Sangcheon’s strengthening sound]
[Suara penguatan Sangcheon]
Wake up, you bastards!
Bangunlah, bajingan!
In times like these, be proud and more confident!
Di saat seperti ini, berbanggalah dan lebih percaya diri!
We have to overcome it head on.
Kita harus mengatasinya secara langsung.
(Gwangshin) So we only have Mr. Roh Can I just believe it?
(Gwangshin) Jadi kita hanya punya Tuan Roh Bolehkah aku mempercayainya?
[Rough breathing]
[Nafas kasar]
Come to your senses, Sangcheon, okay?
Sadarlah, Sangcheon, oke?
[Grunting]
[Mendengus]
[screaming]
[berteriak]
[nervous music]
[musik gugup]
[Sound of moon]
[Suara bulan]
(Nayeon) If possible, please do not use it.
(Nayeon) Jika memungkinkan, mohon jangan menggunakannya.
[Flashlight operation sound]
[Suara pengoperasian senter]
Have you really lived here?
Apakah kamu benar-benar tinggal di sini?
[Soaring music]
[Musik yang melonjak]
[Dark sound effect]
[Efek suara gelap]
[siren sound]
[suara sirene]
(Investigator) On-site verification has been completed.
(Penyidik) Verifikasi di tempat telah selesai.
The body will be moved to the autopsy room.
Jenazah akan dipindahkan ke ruang otopsi.
[rustling sound] Let's check this out
[suara gemerisik] Mari kita periksa ini
Why is the black box in my pocket? I don't know if it came out
Mengapa kotak hitam ada di saku saya? Saya tidak tahu apakah itu keluar
[siren sound]
[suara sirene]
[Car door opens]
[Pintu mobil terbuka]
[Dohan sighs]
[Dohan menghela nafas]
[Nayeon sniffles]
[Nayeon mendengus]
(Dohan) Have you calmed down?
(Dohan) Apakah kamu sudah tenang?
[sigh]
[menghela nafas]
Are you Jaehwang’s brother?
Apakah kamu saudara laki-laki Jaehwang?
[Sighing] Let’s hope something comes out.
[Menghela napas] Semoga saja ada hasilnya.
[heavy music]
[musik berat]
It's probably not suicide
Itu mungkin bukan bunuh diri
I never said it was suicide
Saya tidak pernah mengatakan itu bunuh diri
I think the result will be suicide.
Saya pikir akibatnya adalah bunuh diri.
Although it is a suicide under the circumstances
Meskipun itu adalah bunuh diri dalam situasi seperti itu
The autopsy procedure must be completed It becomes clear
Prosedur otopsi harus diselesaikan Ini menjadi jelas
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[suara ponsel bergetar]
[Bluetooth operating sound] uh
[Suara pengoperasian Bluetooth] eh
(Detective Shin) Team leader I found Deputy Director Kang’s car.
(Detektif Shin) Ketua tim Saya menemukan mobil Wakil Direktur Kang.
It was on the banks of Yangje Stream.
Letaknya di tepi Sungai Yangje.
Detective Park went to check the CCTV.
Detektif Park pergi memeriksa CCTV.
What is the condition of the car?
Bagaimana kondisi mobilnya?
Some of the car windows are broken The black box is completely torn apart.
Beberapa kaca mobil pecah Kotak hitam itu benar-benar terkoyak.
black box
kotak hitam
Just look at the state of the car Under the circumstances, it seems like he was kidnapped.
Lihat saja kondisi mobilnya Dalam keadaan seperti itu, sepertinya dia diculik.
(Dohan) For now, don’t let it be known to the outside world. The search begins with internal personnel.
(Dohan) Untuk saat ini, jangan sampai diketahui dunia luar. Pencarian dimulai dari personel internal.
At the police box near Yangje We ask for your cooperation in finding the missing person.
Di pos polisi dekat Yangje Kami mohon kerjasamanya dalam mencari orang hilang tersebut.
(Dohan) Find it as quickly as possible
(Dohan) Temukan secepat mungkin
yes, i understand
ya saya mengerti
[Call end sound]
[Suara akhir panggilan]
(Detective Shin) Did something come out?
(Detektif Shin) Apakah ada yang keluar?
(Police 1) Nothing has come out yet.
(Polisi 1) Belum ada yang keluar.
Deputy Director Kang kidnapped you? To whom?
Wakil Direktur Kang menculikmu? Kepada siapa?
No way...
Tidak mungkin...
[panicked breathing]
[nafas panik]
But...
Tapi...
You're dead.
kamu sudah mati.
[car horn]
[klakson mobil]
(Jae Hwang) I’m sorry
(Jae Hwang) Maafkan aku
what a person should not do I worked
apa yang tidak boleh dilakukan seseorang saya bekerja
[Jaehwang’s heavy breathing] [dark music]
[Nafas Jaehwang yang berat] [musik gelap]
(Jae Hwang) Due to a moment of anger I committed a sin that cannot be washed away
(Jae Hwang) Karena kemarahan sesaat Saya melakukan dosa yang tidak dapat dihapuskan
To the bereaved families who suffered because of me
Kepada keluarga yang berduka yang menderita karena aku
I apologize.
Saya minta maaf.
I will pay for this sin with my death.
Aku akan membayar dosa ini dengan kematianku.
Mom, I'm sorry
Bu, aku minta maaf
[sigh]
[menghela nafas]
(Man) What is that person?
(Pria) Siapa orang itu?
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Efek suara yang ditekankan]
(Woman 6) What is it? Shouldn’t that person be picked up?
(Wanita 6) Ada apa? Bukankah orang itu harus dijemput?
(Man) Are you crazy? I know what kind of person you are
(Pria) Apakah kamu gila? Saya tahu orang seperti apa Anda
Let's report it to the police.
Mari kita laporkan ke polisi.
(Woman 6) Oh, you must be crazy.
(Wanita 6) Oh, kamu pasti sudah gila.
[Thunder rumbles]
[Guntur bergemuruh]
[siren sound]
[suara sirene]
(Police 2) Please confirm your identity.
(Polisi 2) Harap konfirmasi identitas Anda.
yes
ya
Oh, that’s Magangcheong I heard you are the deputy director, is that correct?
Oh, itu Magangcheong Saya dengar Anda wakil direktur, benarkah?
(Policeman 2) Oh, wallet and all. Well, what can confirm your identity?
(Polisi 2) Oh, dompet dan semuanya. Nah, apa yang bisa mengkonfirmasi identitas Anda?
Because there is nothing
Karena tidak ada apa-apa
yes, that's right
ya itu benar
Is that right, really?
Benarkah?
(Police 2) Hey, but
(Polisi 2) Hei, tapi
But you didn't tell me Why is the conductor on the national highway...
Tapi kamu tidak memberitahuku Mengapa kondektur berada di jalan raya nasional...
Regardless of whether it is a misdemeanor or not It was very dangerous
Terlepas dari apakah itu pelanggaran ringan atau tidak Itu sangat berbahaya
[Sound of approaching footsteps] [dark music]
[Suara langkah kaki mendekat] [musik gelap]
[breathing in relief]
[bernafas lega]
Let's go
Ayo pergi
[sigh]
[menghela nafas]
[Sound of strength]
[Suara kekuatan]
[Jonghun’s sigh]
[Desahan Jonghun]
(Jonghoon) I barely escaped from Jeong Jae-hwang.
(Jonghoon) Saya nyaris lolos dari Jeong Jae-hwang.
(Dohan) Tell me later.
(Dohan) Beritahu aku nanti.
(Nayeon) Is it true?
(Nayeon) Benarkah?
Really Jeong Jae-Hwang Did you kidnap Deputy Director Kang?
Benar-benar Jeong Jae-Hwang Apakah Anda menculik Wakil Direktur Kang?
Why are you here?
Mengapa kamu di sini?
I came to find Jeong Jae-hwang. Nayeon Cheon as well
Saya datang untuk mencari Jeong Jae-hwang. Nayeon Cheon juga
So did you find it?
Jadi, apakah Anda menemukannya?
Already dead when found [Jonghun’s surprised gasp]
Sudah mati saat ditemukan [Jonghun terkesiap kaget]
[Frightened breathing]
[Nafas ketakutan]
(Nayeon) It’s really Jung Jae-hwang Did you kidnap Deputy Director Kang?
(Nayeon) Ini benar-benar Jung Jae-hwang Apakah Anda menculik Wakil Direktur Kang?
[shaking breathing]
[napas gemetar]
(Jonghoon) I’m going in a different car
(Jonghoon) Aku akan naik mobil lain
(Dohan) Please wait a moment.
(Dohan) Mohon tunggu sebentar.
(Jonghun) No, where did you find my car?
(Jonghun) Tidak, di mana kamu menemukan mobilku?
Have you been looking for me all this time?
Apakah selama ini kamu mencariku?
No formal investigation has been filed.
Tidak ada penyelidikan formal yang diajukan.
(Dohan) Wait a minute
(Dohan) Tunggu sebentar
[rustling sound]
[suara gemerisik]
[Car door opens]
[Pintu mobil terbuka]
You have the same thoughts as me right now, right?
Anda memiliki pemikiran yang sama dengan saya saat ini, bukan?
What do you mean?
Apa maksudmu?
‘They say Jeong Jae-hwang was found dead. 'They don't ask how he died'
‘Mereka bilang Jeong Jae-hwang ditemukan tewas. 'Mereka tidak bertanya bagaimana dia meninggal'
That's what you thought, right?
Itu yang Anda pikirkan, bukan?
I didn't think so.
Menurutku tidak.
[Car starting sound]
[Suara start mobil]
[shaking breathing]
[napas gemetar]
[Meaningful music]
[Musik yang bermakna]
(Jonghoon) I barely escaped from Jeong Jae-hwang.
(Jonghoon) Saya nyaris lolos dari Jeong Jae-hwang.
(Dohan) As a result, What did Jeong Jae-hwang get?
(Dohan) Akibatnya, Apa yang didapat Jeong Jae-hwang?
Personal revenge, retribution?
Balas dendam pribadi, pembalasan?
But why did you save the conductor?
Tapi mengapa Anda menyelamatkan kondektur?
(Detective Park) I went.
(Detektif Park) Saya pergi.
(Detective Shin) How are you feeling, Deputy Chief?
(Detektif Shin) Bagaimana perasaanmu, Wakil Kepala?
(Detective Park) You’re feeling better now.
(Detektif Park) Kamu merasa lebih baik sekarang.
Even in hospitals They said there was nothing wrong.
Bahkan di rumah sakit Mereka bilang tidak ada yang salah.
You're going to work tomorrow
Anda akan bekerja besok
A report on the results of the investigation They asked me to wait until two days later.
Laporan hasil penyelidikan Mereka meminta saya menunggu sampai dua hari kemudian.
(Detective Shin) That quickly?
(Detektif Shin) Secepat itu?
(Detective Park) This case You probably want to sort it out quickly.
(Detektif Park) Kasus ini Anda mungkin ingin menyelesaikannya dengan cepat.
Don't you think so?
Bukankah begitu?
Even kidnapped by a criminal I almost died from it
Bahkan diculik oleh penjahat Saya hampir mati karenanya
(Detective Shin) Oh, that I have to write, tsk, stress.
(Detektif Shin) Oh, itu Aku harus menulis, ck, stres.
But the criminal kidnapped the conductor. I really don't understand.
Tapi penjahat itu menculik kondektur. Saya benar-benar tidak mengerti.
(Detective Shin) In charge of the case at that time You used to be a detective, right?
(Detektif Shin) Bertanggung jawab atas kasus ini saat itu Anda dulunya seorang detektif, bukan?
The complainant has a grudge against us. What, once or twice?
Pelapor mempunyai dendam terhadap kami. Apa, sekali atau dua kali?
No, it's gritty.
Tidak, itu berpasir.
(Detective Park) What is this, pooping? I feel like I didn't clean it
(Detektif Park) Apa ini, buang air besar? Sepertinya aku tidak membersihkannya
I have a bad feeling
Aku punya firasat buruk
[dark music] (Detective Shin) I-C, Drupguro. Are you talking about poop? Tsk
[musik gelap] (Detektif Shin) IC, Drupguro. Apakah kamu berbicara tentang kotoran? Ck
All three cases were committed by Jeong Jae-hwang alone. We can organize it, right?
Ketiga kasus tersebut dilakukan oleh Jeong Jae-hwang sendiri. Kita bisa mengaturnya, bukan?
Let’s look at the autopsy results.
Mari kita lihat hasil otopsinya.
You contacted Jeong Jae-hwang’s mother, right?
Anda menghubungi ibu Jeong Jae-hwang, kan?
(Detective Shin) Yes, you arrived a little while ago.
(Detektif Shin) Ya, Anda tiba beberapa waktu yang lalu.
[heavy music]
[musik berat]
[The Emperor’s mother sobs]
[Ibu Kaisar terisak]
Jaehwang!
Jaehwang!
(Jae-hwang’s mother) Mom is here, Jae-hwang.
(Ibu Jae-hwang) Ibu ada di sini, Jae-hwang.
wake up
bangun
Mom is here, Jaehwang, mom is here...
Ibu di sini, Jaehwang, ibu di sini...
[The emperor's mother cries]
[Ibu Kaisar menangis]
[Sobbing]
[Menangis]
[sniffles]
[mendengus]
[Continued sobbing]
[Terus menangis]
(Nayeon) When will this nightmare end?
(Nayeon) Kapan mimpi buruk ini akan berakhir?
(Nayeon) I’m sorry, mom, I’m sorry
(Nayeon) Maafkan aku, bu, aku minta maaf
My father died because of my mother's mistake.
Ayahku meninggal karena kesalahan ibuku.
Our Nayeon too
Nayeon kami juga
Dragging me into this nightmare
Menyeretku ke dalam mimpi buruk ini
I'm sorry
aku minta maaf
Don't say that anymore, Mom.
Jangan katakan itu lagi, Bu.
[Bird chirping]
[Kicau burung]
(Anchor 2 in the news) Yangje-gun, Gangwon-do In an abandoned house
(Penyiar 2 dalam berita) Yangje-gun, Gangwon-do Di sebuah rumah yang ditinggalkan
The body of a man in his 30s was found.
Mayat seorang pria berusia 30-an ditemukan.
[The door swings open] According to the police, he committed suicide This man, who is believed to have quit
[Pintunya terbuka] Menurut polisi, dia bunuh diri Pria ini, yang diyakini telah berhenti
[dark music] City Councilor Park Kwang-shin, who recently took place as a suspect in a murder case
[musik gelap] Anggota Dewan Kota Park Kwang-shin, yang baru saja menjabat sebagai tersangka kasus pembunuhan
It is reported that he was tracked
Dilaporkan bahwa dia dilacak
Meanwhile, the police recently Whether or not it is related to other murder cases
Sementara itu, polisi baru-baru ini Apakah ada hubungannya dengan kasus pembunuhan lainnya atau tidak
It is said to be under investigation.
Dikatakan sedang diselidiki.
(Byungjun) So
(Byungjun) Jadi
Where is Jaehwang’s funeral?
Dimana pemakaman Jaehwang?
(Yeon-gwang) [Sighing] The body is still there I didn't get it, but
(Yeon-gwang) [Menghela nafas] Tubuhnya masih di sana Aku tidak mengerti, tapi
The police need to complete the autopsy They said they could hand over the body.
Polisi perlu menyelesaikan otopsi Mereka bilang mereka bisa menyerahkan jenazahnya.
(Reunion) Ah, you fool
(Reuni) Ah, bodoh
Why die?
Mengapa mati?
Are you dying because you did something wrong?
Apakah Anda sekarat karena Anda melakukan kesalahan?
[Yeon-gwang and the sigh of reunion]
[Yeon-gwang dan desahan reuni]
(Cheongju’s house) He’s truly a reigning emperor. Was that what you were thinking about?
(Rumah Cheongju) Dia benar-benar seorang kaisar yang berkuasa. Itukah yang kamu pikirkan?
I shouldn't have told you in advance
Aku seharusnya tidak memberitahumu sebelumnya
What if I said it? What changes?
Bagaimana jika saya mengatakannya? Perubahan apa?
(Cheongju’s house) Ah, but If we all acted together
(Rumah Cheongju) Ah, tapi Jika kita semua bertindak bersama-sama
It would have been a little less difficult...
Itu akan menjadi sedikit lebih mudah...
That's it!
Itu dia!
Even if that idiot bastard dies, it's worth it.
Biarpun bajingan idiot itu mati, itu sepadan.
stop talking
berhenti bicara
[Cheongju’s sigh]
[Desah Cheongju]
(Autopsy) Cause of death Asphyxiation due to cervical compression
(Otopsi) Penyebab kematian Asfiksia akibat kompresi serviks
And the line here causes The scar marks end below your ears, right?
Dan garis di sini menyebabkan Bekas lukanya berakhir di bawah telingamu, kan?
He died by hanging, right?
Dia mati dengan cara digantung, kan?
Is it suicide?
Apakah itu bunuh diri?
(Autopsy) No, on the cell phone I heard there was a will too?
(Otopsi) Tidak, di ponsel Kudengar ada surat wasiat juga?
There must also be forensic evidence.
Juga harus ada bukti forensik.
[Autopsy doctor's faint smile]
[Senyum tipis dokter otopsi]
After all, I like things that are certain. What about our old version?
Lagipula, aku menyukai hal-hal yang pasti. Bagaimana dengan versi lama kami?
It's been a long time since I became a police officer.
Sudah lama sekali saya tidak menjadi polisi.
(of autopsy) I know, I know Our former team leader
(otopsi) Saya tahu, saya tahu Mantan pemimpin tim kami
Look again at the scar marks here, isn’t it clean?
Coba lihat lagi bekas luka disini, bersih kan?
Hanging on a rope until I lose my breath It's proof that I waited patiently
Bergantung pada tali sampai aku kehabisan nafas Itu bukti aku menunggu dengan sabar
In case of murder Because the area around this scar is dirty.
Dalam kasus pembunuhan Pasalnya, area sekitar bekas luka ini kotor.
Because I'm struggling to survive
Karena aku sedang berjuang untuk bertahan hidup
And the fingerprints found on the string Footprints found on a chair
Dan sidik jarinya ditemukan pada tali itu Jejak kaki ditemukan di kursi
Only suspects
Hanya tersangka
So it's suicide
Jadi itu bunuh diri
But that's right
Tapi itu benar
There are traces of bruises
Ada bekas lebam
That also happened right before I died.
Itu juga terjadi tepat sebelum saya meninggal.
Well, it's not a beating. It was probably just a light fight.
Yah, itu bukan pemukulan. Itu mungkin hanya pertarungan ringan.
If it was a physical fight, then when the conductor was kidnapped...
Jika itu perkelahian fisik, maka ketika kondektur diculik...
(Autopsy) Hmm? Kidnapping?
(Otopsi) Hmm? Penculikan?
(Dohan) Oh, no.
(Dohan) Oh tidak.
I don't know what you're talking about Because I have to judge based on the body alone.
Saya tidak tahu apa yang Anda bicarakan Karena saya harus menilai berdasarkan badannya saja.
In my opinion as a forensic scientist,
Menurut pendapat saya sebagai ilmuwan forensik,
Asphyxiation certain, suicide certain.
Pasti sesak napas, bunuh diri pasti.
(Autopsy) Well, judging by the bruises
(Otopsi) Ya, dilihat dari memarnya
There was a slight struggle before death.
Ada sedikit perjuangan sebelum kematian.
I'm here
saya di sini
Next is our old team leader.
Berikutnya adalah pemimpin tim lama kita.
(Jae Hwang) If you let me go, Deputy Director Kang. [Dark sound effect]
(Jae Hwang) Jika Anda melepaskan saya, Wakil Direktur Kang. [Efek suara gelap]
[Screaming scared]
[Berteriak ketakutan]
(Jae Hwang) Are you telling the truth while reflecting?
(Jae Hwang) Apakah kamu mengatakan kebenaran sambil merenung?
[Knocking sound]
[Suara ketukan]
[sigh]
[menghela nafas]
[Jonghoon slams the drawer shut]
[Jonghoon membanting laci hingga tertutup]
(Dohan) The autopsy results came out.
(Dohan) Hasil otopsi keluar.
(Jonghun) Uh, what’s special about it?
(Jonghun) Eh, apa istimewanya itu?
(Dohan) Before or after the kidnapping? Was there a physical fight with Jeong Jae-hwang?
(Dohan) Sebelum atau sesudah penculikan? Apakah ada perkelahian fisik dengan Jeong Jae-hwang?
There was
Ada
(Dohan) Aside from the teacher’s mark on my neck, They say there were bruises
(Dohan) Selain tanda guru di leherku, Mereka bilang ada memar
I think there was a fight with the conductor. Do you mind if I understand?
Saya pikir ada perkelahian dengan kondektur. Apakah kamu keberatan jika aku mengerti?
[dark music]
[musik gelap]
(Sangdo) Don’t be too obsessed with Jeong Jae-hwang.
(Sangdo) Jangan terlalu terobsesi dengan Jeong Jae-hwang.
Committing murder now
Melakukan pembunuhan sekarang
It may not be Jeong Jae-hwang.
Itu mungkin bukan Jeong Jae-hwang.
What's going on?
Apa yang terjadi?
I don't know either
Saya juga tidak tahu
me too
saya juga
(Dohan) Place of kidnapping
(Dohan) Tempat penculikan
Are you still embarrassed to talk?
Apakah kamu masih malu untuk berbicara?
Shouldn’t we at least check the CCTV?
Bukankah sebaiknya kita setidaknya memeriksa CCTV?
I went there for personal business.
Saya pergi ke sana untuk urusan pribadi.
(Jong-Hoon) And a person as high as a deputy chief
(Jong-Hoon) Dan seseorang setinggi wakil kepala
Kidnapped by a criminal If it is known that you have been harmed
Diculik oleh penjahat Jika diketahui bahwa Anda telah dirugikan
It looks so funny
Kelihatannya lucu sekali
(Dohan) I understand.
(Dohan) Saya mengerti.
So these three murder cases
Jadi tiga kasus pembunuhan ini
When the suspect dies
Saat tersangka meninggal
With no right of prosecution I'm trying to finish it
Tanpa hak penuntutan Saya mencoba menyelesaikannya
Good job, let's go
Kerja bagus, ayo pergi
(Jonghun) Why? Is there anything else you want to say?
(Jonghun) Kenapa? Apakah ada hal lain yang ingin Anda katakan?
I gave my official opinion
Saya memberikan pendapat resmi saya
Now I will tell you my personal opinion.
Sekarang saya akan memberi tahu Anda pendapat pribadi saya.
(Dohan) This is also for the deputy director I think you should know
(Dohan) Ini juga untuk wakil direktur Saya pikir Anda harus tahu
As a detective, I need to dig deeper.
Sebagai seorang detektif, saya perlu menggali lebih dalam.
As a lawyer, ‘This is enough. 'It's enough to just cover it up'
Sebagai seorang pengacara, ‘Ini sudah cukup. 'Cukup untuk menutupinya saja'
That kind of judgment came out It's about finishing it.
Penghakiman seperti itu muncul Ini tentang menyelesaikannya.
What do you mean, that?
Apa maksudmu itu?
(Dohan) The reason you put me in this case in the first place is
(Dohan) Alasan pertama Anda memasukkan saya ke dalam kasus ini adalah
I wanted Goo Do-han, who was a lawyer.
Saya menginginkan Goo Do-han, yang merupakan seorang pengacara.
Isn't it?
Bukan?
(Jonghun) We have to dig into it persistently. You'll just have to roughly cover it up
(Jonghun) Kita harus terus menggalinya. Anda hanya perlu menutupinya secara kasar
I'm good at distinguishing
Saya pandai membedakan
[Laughing] Don't you know?
[Tertawa] Tahukah kamu?
The lawyer said that They are specialized races
Pengacara mengatakan itu Mereka adalah ras yang terspesialisasi
Well, you don't have to worry.
Nah, Anda tidak perlu khawatir.
(Dohan) Is it okay to do this?
(Dohan) Bolehkah melakukan ini?
If it ends like this Is everyone happy?
Jika berakhir seperti ini Apakah semua orang bahagia?
[siren sound]
[suara sirene]
(Detective Park) This case also It's organized like this
(Detektif Park) Kasus ini juga Ini diatur seperti ini
It was tough, it was tough.
Itu sulit, itu sulit.
(Detective Shin) From the victims’ group
(Detektif Shin) Dari kelompok korban
Even if he didn't appear at every murder scene.
Meski dia tidak muncul di setiap lokasi pembunuhan.
It would have been much easier
Akan jauh lebih mudah
Mr. I, you properly caused confusion in the investigation.
Tuan I, Anda benar-benar menyebabkan kebingungan dalam penyelidikan.
(Detective Park) So, Byungjun Lee is that person.
(Detektif Park) Jadi, Byungjun Lee adalah orang itu.
For obstruction of investigation It should have been thrown in.
Untuk menghalangi penyelidikan Seharusnya itu dimasukkan ke dalam.
(Detective Shin) No more Because there were no victims
(Detektif Shin) Tidak lagi Sebab, tidak ada korban jiwa
Fortunately, yes
Untungnya, ya
If Deputy Kang got hit too Was it obvious?
Jika Wakil Kang tertabrak juga Apakah sudah jelas?
(Detective Park) Then the entire police There's an uproar
(Detektif Park) Lalu seluruh polisi Ada keributan
Now only the investigation results report Just write it and you're done.
Sekarang hanya laporan hasil investigasi Tulis saja dan selesai.
have a hard time
mengalami kesulitan
(Detective Shin) [Sighing] Ah, yes.
(Detektif Shin) [Menghela napas] Ah, ya.
(Dohan) Do you really think it’s the end?
(Dohan) Apakah menurut Anda ini adalah akhirnya?
(Detective Shin) Yes?
(Detektif Shin) Ya?
Be sure to write a report on the results of the investigation
Pastikan untuk menulis laporan tentang hasil penyelidikan
(Dohan) Senior, you are also doing the same.
(Dohan) Senior, kamu juga melakukan hal yang sama.
These two people are different from me
Kedua orang ini berbeda dari saya
Dig into any doubt until the end
Gali keraguan apa pun sampai akhir
have to prove
harus membuktikan
Don't forget that you were born a detective.
Jangan lupa bahwa Anda terlahir sebagai detektif.
(Detective Park) I understand.
(Detektif Park) Saya mengerti.
(Detective Shin) I understand.
(Detektif Shin) Saya mengerti.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[suara ponsel bergetar]
yes
ya
You're not sorting out the case like this, are you?
Anda tidak menyelesaikan kasus seperti ini, bukan?
What more should I do?
Apa lagi yang harus saya lakukan?
We have to follow the traces of the suspect.
Kita harus mengikuti jejak tersangka.
You're dead.
kamu sudah mati.
(Dohan) Due to the death of the suspect It was processed as there was no right to prosecute.
(Dohan) Karena kematian tersangka Itu diproses karena tidak ada hak untuk menuntut.
There's no reason to follow the trail
Tidak ada alasan untuk mengikuti jejaknya
Kidnapped by Jeong Jae-hwang There is also a statement from Deputy Director Kang.
Diculik oleh Jeong Jae-hwang Ada juga pernyataan dari Wakil Direktur Kang.
What about the evidence?
Bagaimana dengan buktinya?
Proof that they were all done by Jeong Jae-hwang. Is it enough?
Buktinya semuanya dilakukan oleh Jeong Jae-hwang. Apakah itu cukup?
(Nayeon) Because I recognized it Even if the suspect dies
(Nayeon) Karena aku mengenalinya Bahkan jika tersangkanya meninggal
There is clear evidence that he is the culprit. It seemed like the principle was to secure it.
Ada bukti jelas bahwa dialah pelakunya. Sepertinya prinsipnya adalah mengamankannya.
Hey, are you a police officer?
Hei, apakah kamu seorang polisi?
To cover up the incident like this It was put in, right?
Untuk menutupi kejadian seperti ini Itu sudah dimasukkan, kan?
(Nayeon) In the first place, Team Leader Koo’s role was It was decided that way, right?
(Nayeon) Pertama-tama, peran Ketua Tim Koo adalah Sudah diputuskan seperti itu, bukan?
Don't pass it up.
Jangan lewatkan itu.
(Nayeon) Well, it doesn’t matter anymore
(Nayeon) Ya, itu tidak penting lagi
If the police won't do it, I have to do it.
Jika polisi tidak mau melakukannya, saya harus melakukannya.
Not once or twice
Tidak sekali atau dua kali
I'm going to follow Jaehwang's traces.
Saya akan mengikuti jejak Jaehwang.
What do you mean? What are you doing now?
Apa maksudmu? Kamu sedang apa sekarang
(Nayeon) Victim and fraudster
(Nayeon) Korban dan penipu
Jaehwang's brother is released from prison The person I went to meet
Kakak Jaehwang dibebaskan dari penjara Orang yang saya temui
(Nayeon) Let’s figure it out from there.
(Nayeon) Mari kita cari tahu dari sana.
We were supposed to meet together
Kami seharusnya bertemu bersama
But the old team leader said the situation has changed.
Namun pemimpin tim lama mengatakan situasinya telah berubah.
I have to meet him alone.
Aku harus menemuinya sendirian.
Where are you now?
Kamu ada di mana sekarang?
[Call end sound]
[Suara akhir panggilan]
[Dark sound effect]
[Efek suara gelap]
(Employee) How did you come?
(Karyawan) Bagaimana Anda bisa datang?
(Nayeon) I came to meet the CEO.
(Nayeon) Saya datang menemui CEO.
(Employee) Did you promise?
(Karyawan) Apakah Anda berjanji?
(Nayeon) My name is Nayeon Cheon Just tell it to me.
(Nayeon) Namaku Nayeon Cheon Katakan saja padaku.
(Employee) Oh, yes, you are in a meeting right now.
(Karyawan) Oh ya, Anda sedang rapat sekarang.
I'll guide you when it's finished.
Saya akan memandu Anda jika sudah selesai.
(Dohan) Don’t misunderstand. came here
(Dohan) Jangan salah paham. datang ke sini
not because of the evidence
bukan karena buktinya
Na-yeon Cheon is useless. I followed you because I was afraid you might get stirred up.
Na-yeon Cheon tidak berguna. Aku mengikutimu karena aku takut kamu akan terguncang.
(Nayeon) Um, did you come to keep an eye on me?
(Nayeon) Um, apakah kamu datang untuk mengawasiku?
Then go back
Lalu kembali
Because it’s still not too late
Karena ini masih belum terlambat
[The door clicks open] [Dajeong’s happy exclamation]
[Pintunya terbuka] [Seruan gembira Dajeong]
(affectionately) Oh my!
(dengan penuh kasih sayang) Ya ampun!
Oh my god, who is this?
Ya Tuhan, siapa ini?
[affectionate laughter]
[tertawa penuh kasih sayang]
- It's been a while. - (Sweet) Yes, Nayeon.
- Sudah lama tidak bertemu. - (Manis) Ya, Nayeon.
(Sweet) Oh my, she’s such a baby I see today that it’s time to get married?
(Manis) Ya ampun, dia masih bayi Saya mengerti hari ini bahwa sudah waktunya untuk menikah?
[Small] Who are you? Maybe a boyfriend?
[Kecil] Siapa kamu? Mungkin pacar?
(Dohan) I...
(Dohan) aku...
This is the team leader who rescued Kang Su-dae.
Ini adalah ketua tim yang menyelamatkan Kang Su-dae.
(Dajeong) What are you? Why do you have police around?
(Dajeong) Siapa kamu? Mengapa ada polisi di sekitarmu?
Jaehwang oppa was here, right?
Jaehwang oppa ada di sini, kan?
Jaehwang? Jaehwang Jeong?
Jaehwang? Jaehwang Jeong?
-Why him? - (Dohan) I will ask.
-Kenapa dia? - (Dohan) Saya akan bertanya.
(Do-han) You met Jeong Jae-hwang, right?
(Do-han) Anda bertemu Jeong Jae-hwang, kan?
I don't remember much
Saya tidak ingat banyak
You know it's our job
Anda tahu itu tugas kami
(affectionately) the original person Since we meet a lot,
(dengan penuh kasih sayang) orang aslinya Karena kita sering bertemu,
Before I came here, I had a prison visitation record. I did some searching
Sebelum saya datang ke sini, saya memiliki catatan kunjungan penjara. Saya melakukan pencarian
(Do-han) Mr. Han Da-jeong Jaehwang Jeong, one month before his release from prison
(Do-han) Tuan Han Da-jeong Jaehwang Jeong, satu bulan sebelum dibebaskan dari penjara
There is a record of the visit.
Ada catatan kunjungan tersebut.
According to Jaehwang’s mother,
Menurut ibu Jaehwang,
After being released from prison, I met Han Da-jeong. We were supposed to meet
Setelah dibebaskan dari penjara, saya bertemu Han Da-jeong. Kami seharusnya bertemu
(affectionately) Ah, I remember now
(dengan penuh kasih sayang) Ah, aku ingat sekarang
That Jeong Jae-hwang?
Jeong Jae-hwang itu?
[laughter]
[tertawa]
After Jaehwang is released from prison I asked you to do some work together, I
Setelah Jaehwang dibebaskan dari penjara Saya meminta Anda untuk melakukan beberapa pekerjaan bersama, saya
As you know
Seperti yang Anda tahu
This thing is You need a lot of trustworthy people.
Hal ini adalah Anda membutuhkan banyak orang yang dapat dipercaya.
You said you wanted to do multi-step work together?
Anda bilang ingin melakukan pekerjaan multi-langkah bersama?
[Interesting music] (affectionately) Ah, boy, it’s a multi-level scheme.
[Musik yang menarik] (dengan penuh kasih sayang) Ah, nak, ini adalah skema multi-level.
It's definitely a coin business, this is
Ini pasti bisnis koin, ini
Don't you know the coin?
Apakah kamu tidak tahu koinnya?
These days, if you don't know coins, you're a fool. [laughter]
Saat ini, jika Anda tidak tahu koin, Anda bodoh. [tertawa]
You will do it in multiple steps using coins.
Anda akan melakukannya dalam beberapa langkah menggunakan koin.
(Nayeon) Jeon You are in the solar energy investment business.
(Nayeon) Jeon Anda berada dalam bisnis investasi energi surya.
You're so fashionable
Kamu sangat modis
You have to be fast these days
Anda harus cepat hari ini
(Dajeong) This market is also trendy It changes so quickly
(Dajeong) Pasar ini juga trendi Itu berubah begitu cepat
Well, in a few days we We are holding a large coin investment briefing session.
Ya, dalam beberapa hari kita Kami mengadakan sesi pengarahan investasi koin besar-besaran.
You should come too
Anda harus datang juga
[affectionate laughter]
[tertawa penuh kasih sayang]
[Dajeong’s surprised exclamation]
[Seruan terkejut Dajeong]
What are you, how much does it cost?
Apa kamu, berapa biayanya?
(Dohan) Coins and solar energy You make it very trendy.
(Dohan) Koin dan energi matahari Anda membuatnya sangat trendi.
This one is broken Will it be a 1 degree hit?
Yang ini rusak Apakah ini akan mencapai 1 derajat?
[Dajeong’s surprised exclamation]
[Seruan terkejut Dajeong]
During the wellness boom, you also did health food, right?
Selama booming kesehatan, Anda juga melakukan makanan kesehatan, bukan?
(Dajeong) How do you know that?
(Dajeong) Bagaimana kamu tahu itu?
(Nayeon) Team leader Koo [Dajeong’s surprised exclamation]
(Nayeon) Ketua tim Koo [Seruan terkejut Dajeong]
(Dajeong) What are you doing?
(Dajeong) Apa yang kamu lakukan?
Is it all about being a police officer?
Apakah ini semua tentang menjadi petugas polisi?
To a good businessman What are you doing?
Untuk seorang pengusaha yang baik Apa yang kamu lakukan?
[Nayeon’s sigh] (Dohan) Goodness?
[Nayeon menghela nafas] (Dohan) Ya ampun?
(affectionately) Yes
(dengan penuh kasih sayang) Ya
(Dohan) Your eyes, those eyes [Interesting music]
(Dohan) Matamu, mata itu [Musik yang menarik]
What? Eye color?
Apa? Warna mata?
(Dohan) I’m on the verge of passing now.
(Dohan) Saya hampir meninggal sekarang.
What do you mean my eye color is beyond this?
Apa maksudmu warna mataku melebihi ini?
You have the eyes to go from a fraudster to a murderer.
Anda memiliki keinginan untuk beralih dari penipu menjadi pembunuh.
What are you talking about? unluckily
Apa yang kamu bicarakan? sayangnya
If you keep going like this, you'll cross that line
Jika Anda terus seperti ini, Anda akan melewati batas itu
Hey, even if I cheat No murder, Mr.
Hei, meskipun aku curang Tidak ada pembunuhan, Pak.
(affectionately) Everyone get out!
(dengan penuh kasih sayang) Semuanya keluar!
see you later
sampai jumpa lagi
(Nayeon) Wait a minute
(Nayeon) Tunggu sebentar
What did Jaehwang oppa say, so?
Jadi apa yang Jaehwang oppa katakan?
(affectionately) I refuse You cut off contact with me, is that okay?
(dengan penuh kasih sayang) saya menolak Anda memutuskan kontak dengan saya, apakah tidak apa-apa?
Everyone get out!
Semuanya keluar!
[Sigh of sweetness]
[Menghela napas manis]
[Rough breathing]
[Nafas kasar]
[screaming indignantly]
[berteriak dengan marah]
Those are the seeds
Itulah benihnya
Ah, ah, what should I do with this?
Ah, ah, apa yang harus kulakukan dengan ini?
[Nayeon’s exasperated breathing]
[Napas Nayeon yang jengkel]
(Nayeon) Why did you do that?
(Nayeon) Kenapa kamu melakukan itu?
I saw it for the first time Team leader Koo is so excited
Saya melihatnya untuk pertama kalinya Ketua tim Koo sangat bersemangat
There wasn't much success.
Tidak banyak keberhasilan yang dicapai.
I'm sorry, I asked you to come here for no reason.
Maaf, saya meminta Anda untuk datang ke sini tanpa alasan.
It's a waste of time
Ini hanya membuang-buang waktu
Do you still believe the scammers? Even after being treated like that?
Apakah Anda masih percaya scammers? Bahkan setelah diperlakukan seperti itu?
(Dohan) Cheon Na-yeon, are you stupid?
(Dohan) Cheon Na-yeon, apakah kamu bodoh?
It's a lie just by looking at it Talking about Jeong Jae-Hwang
Itu bohong hanya dengan melihatnya Berbicara tentang Jeong Jae-Hwang
[Sighing] That human I also know someone
[Menghela nafas] Manusia itu Saya juga kenal seseorang
That person may not remember me, but
Orang itu mungkin tidak mengingatku, tapi
How do you know?
Bagaimana kamu tahu?
Rather, that woman is the victim. The word fraudster
Sebaliknya, wanita itu adalah korbannya. Kata penipu
tell me what that means
beritahu aku apa maksudnya
Not all victims are good people.
Tidak semua korban adalah orang baik.
Hey, bitch, just snap this!
Hei, jalang, ambil saja ini!
[People stop]
[Orang-orang berhenti]
[Da-jeong’s angry breathing] (Jae Hwang) Please stop.
[Napas marah Da-jeong] (Jae Hwang) Tolong hentikan.
[Meaningful music] What Noh Sang-cheon caught, that was all wrong.
[Musik yang bermakna] Apa yang ditangkap Noh Sang-cheon, itu semua salah.
(Dajeong) I can’t trust the police, I can’t trust anyone.
(Dajeong) Saya tidak bisa mempercayai polisi, saya tidak bisa mempercayai siapa pun.
Everyone takes care of the stolen money. I have no choice but to make up for it.
Semua orang mengurus uang yang dicuri. Saya tidak punya pilihan selain menebusnya.
(Nayeon) Because I was scammed It's true that I was definitely harmed, but
(Nayeon) Karena saya ditipu Memang benar aku benar-benar dirugikan, tapi
Even people It doesn't mean I'm a good person. [Dajeong persuades]
Bahkan orang-orang Bukan berarti aku orang baik. [Dajeong membujuk]
And Han Da-jeong
Dan Han Da-jeong
I changed my name
Saya mengubah nama saya
Original name is Han Chun-ja
Nama aslinya adalah Han Chun-ja
(Nayeon) Do you know that? [Dajeong explains]
(Nayeon) Tahukah kamu itu? [Dajeong menjelaskan]
Among those who have suffered damage at multiple levels
Di antara mereka yang menderita kerusakan di berbagai tingkatan
Someone who jumps into multi-level marketing again The fact is that there are quite a few.
Seseorang yang terjun ke pemasaran berjenjang lagi Faktanya jumlahnya cukup banyak.
I found out after being scammed.
Saya mengetahuinya setelah ditipu.
'If you start before others 'You can make money' [affectionate laughter]
'Jika kamu memulai sebelum orang lain 'Kamu bisa menghasilkan uang' [tertawa penuh kasih sayang]
I'm that famous
Aku setenar itu
I am a victim of the Noh Sang-cheon fraud case.
Saya adalah korban kasus penipuan Noh Sang-cheon.
[People's surprised exclamations]
[Seruan kaget orang-orang]
But this business is different
Namun bisnis ini berbeda
Network business...
Bisnis jaringan...
[Dajeong continues explaining] (Nayeon) That’s what a Ponzi scheme is like.
[Dajeong terus menjelaskan] (Nayeon) Seperti itulah skema Ponzi.
People who started late get paid Giving money to the person who started first
Orang yang terlambat memulai akan dibayar Memberikan uang kepada orang yang memulai terlebih dahulu
By creating a completely new multi-level
Dengan menciptakan multi-level yang benar-benar baru
faster than anyone else I became a fraudster.
lebih cepat dari orang lain Saya menjadi penipu.
That way you can Making up for the money that was scammed
Dengan begitu Anda bisa Mengganti uang yang ditipu
Justifying yourself
Membenarkan diri sendiri
Increasingly, in that black swamp I fall deep
Semakin lama, di rawa hitam itu Aku terjatuh dalam-dalam
Now on my face A new stigma is created
Sekarang di wajahku Stigma baru pun tercipta
(Nayeon) You’re a fraud
(Nayeon) Kamu penipu
[Call connection tone]
[Nada sambungan panggilan]
close
dekat
What kind of idiot A police officer went
Orang bodoh macam apa Seorang petugas polisi pergi
They say it's Gu Do-han.
Mereka bilang itu Gu Do-han.
No, specifically to investigate. It didn't seem like it came out.
Tidak, khusus untuk menyelidiki. Sepertinya itu tidak keluar.
But really to me You're not going to be harmed, right?
Tapi sungguh bagiku Anda tidak akan dirugikan, bukan?
I did what I was told.
Saya melakukan apa yang diperintahkan.
But
Tapi
Why did Jaehwang commit suicide...
Mengapa Jaehwang bunuh diri...
[Call end sound]
[Suara akhir panggilan]
[dark music] Are you still doing this?
[musik gelap] Apakah kamu masih melakukan ini?
(Jae Hwang) He told me to come find him when I get out of prison.
(Jae Hwang) Dia menyuruhku untuk datang menemuinya ketika aku keluar dari penjara.
I just want help with this Is that it?
Saya hanya ingin bantuan dalam hal ini Apakah itu saja?
[light laughter]
[tertawa ringan]
It's not like that
Bukan seperti itu
(Dajeong) You said you wanted to farm when you get out of prison.
(Dajeong) Kamu bilang kamu ingin bertani ketika kamu keluar dari penjara.
My friend who has an empty house in the countryside i want to help you
Teman saya yang memiliki rumah kosong di pedesaan saya ingin membantu kamu
go here
pergi ke sini
[Rustling sound]
[Suara gemerisik]
[Sighing] Well, but
[Menghela napas] Ya, tapi
Even if I think about our old days You can't do this.
Bahkan jika aku memikirkan masa lalu kita Anda tidak bisa melakukan ini.
(Jae Hwang) This is Noh Sang-cheon’s scam. What's different?
(Jae Hwang) Ini adalah penipuan Noh Sang-cheon. Apa yang berbeda?
What does it matter to you
Apa pentingnya bagi Anda
(Sweet) And is that the list? I heard I'm in on something too
(Manis) Dan apakah itu daftarnya? Kudengar aku juga terlibat dalam sesuatu
Write such a strange list You shouldn't do that either.
Tulis daftar yang aneh Anda juga tidak boleh melakukan itu.
Forget the dark past Let's live towards a bright future
Lupakan masa lalu yang kelam Mari kita hidup menuju masa depan yang cerah
Huh?
Hah?
[Crying] Who am I? How did I end up in jail?
[Menangis] Siapa aku? Bagaimana saya bisa masuk penjara?
Have you completely forgotten?
Apakah kamu benar-benar lupa?
Let's forget about that now
Mari kita lupakan hal itu sekarang
How could you forget that!
Bagaimana kamu bisa melupakan itu!
(Jae Hwang) Mr. Lee! [eerie music]
(Jae Hwang) Tuan Lee! [musik menakutkan]
[shaking breathing]
[napas gemetar]
Now, team leader, tell me
Sekarang, ketua tim, beritahu saya
(Nayeon) Han Da-jeong, CEO of Multilevel How do you know this person?
(Nayeon) Han Da-jeong, CEO Multilevel Bagaimana Anda mengenal orang ini?
Did you conduct an illegal multi-level investigation?
Apakah Anda melakukan investigasi multi-level ilegal?
I had a younger sister
Saya memiliki seorang adik perempuan
The only family I had left
Satu-satunya keluarga yang tersisa bagiku
There was?
Ada?
[camera shutter sound] [dark music]
[suara rana kamera] [musik gelap]
dead
mati
Murdered, 7 years ago
Dibunuh, 7 tahun lalu
Did you catch the culprit?
Apakah Anda menangkap pelakunya?
In the past, that person, Han Chun-ja, He was a relevant person.
Di masa lalu, orang itu, Han Chun-ja, Dia adalah orang yang relevan.
the culprit
pelakunya
How are you involved?
Bagaimana Anda terlibat?
How do you know Han Da-jeong? I think I got the answer
Bagaimana kamu tahu Han Da-jeong? Saya pikir saya mendapat jawabannya
(Dohan) Other than that, on the topic Since I'm out of the way, I have no obligation to answer.
(Dohan) Selain itu, pada topik Karena saya menyingkir, saya tidak punya kewajiban untuk menjawab.
Rather, do you remember the Song Young-jin incident?
Sebaliknya, apakah Anda ingat kejadian Song Young-jin?
Ordered from a Chinese restaurant They deliberately made the body be discovered.
Dipesan dari restoran Cina Mereka sengaja membuat jenazahnya ditemukan.
It was like that
Seperti itulah
Isn't it similar?
Mirip bukan?
(Dohan) I sent a courier to Jeong Jae-hwang. What I discovered on purpose
(Dohan) Saya mengirim kurir ke Jeong Jae-hwang. Apa yang saya temukan dengan sengaja
That's
Itu
Jaehwang oppa to find myself dead
Jaehwang oppa untuk menemukan diriku mati
(Nayeon) Isn’t that something you do yourself?
(Nayeon) Bukankah itu sesuatu yang kamu lakukan sendiri?
Even if you die there, no one will know
Bahkan jika kamu mati di sana, tidak akan ada yang tahu
He committed suicide by hanging his mother. You want me to find your own body?
Dia bunuh diri dengan menggantung ibunya. Anda ingin saya menemukan tubuh Anda sendiri?
Mr. Jeong Jae-hwang like that Isn't that a bad thing?
Tuan Jeong Jae-hwang seperti itu Bukankah itu hal yang buruk?
I thought a lot about mom
Aku banyak memikirkan tentang ibu
When I think of my mother who is left alone
Saat aku memikirkan ibuku yang ditinggal sendirian
I'm not the kind of person who would commit suicide in the first place.
Saya bukan tipe orang yang akan bunuh diri.
Han Da-jeong, that woman
Han Da-jeong, wanita itu
It was clear that he had a certain role.
Jelas sekali dia mempunyai peran tertentu.
(Dohan) Ha, I’m hiding it.
(Dohan) Ha, saya menyembunyikannya.
What on earth is that?
Apa itu?
How did the case end? Does that sound like a no?
Bagaimana akhir kasusnya? Apakah itu terdengar seperti tidak?
(Vocal cords) Tell me
(Pita suara) Katakan padaku
It's a pity, but I have a meeting. I don't think we'll be able to talk for long
Sayang sekali, tapi aku ada rapat. Saya rasa kita tidak akan bisa berbicara lama
Yeah, well, it just takes a moment.
Ya, itu hanya butuh beberapa saat.
By the way, do you know Jeong So-ram?
Ngomong-ngomong, apakah kamu kenal Jeong So-ram?
Jeong So-ram?
Jeong So Ram?
(Vocal cord) Yes, our office I was an employee [Dark sound effect]
(Pita suara) Ya, kantor kami Saya adalah seorang karyawan [Efek suara gelap]
It's already been a few years
Sudah beberapa tahun berlalu
(Jonghoon) Um...
(Jonghoon) Um...
Then recently, separately, like this You've never contacted me?
Lalu baru-baru ini, secara terpisah, seperti ini Anda belum pernah menghubungi saya?
Well, I don't remember
Yah, aku tidak ingat
For what reason?
Untuk alasan apa?
Do you know Noh Sang-cheon?
Tahukah kamu Noh Sang Cheon?
It's Nosangcheon Well, I think I've heard of it.
Itu Nosangcheon Yah, sepertinya aku pernah mendengarnya.
Well, it hasn't become much of an issue yet.
Yah, itu belum menjadi masalah besar.
(Jonghoon) He, for fraud. He's a wanted person right now.
(Jonghoon) Dia, untuk penipuan. Dia adalah orang yang dicari saat ini.
But Jeong So-ram worked at Noh Sang-cheon’s company.
Tapi Jeong So-ram bekerja di perusahaan Noh Sang-cheon.
He was working as a key executive.
Dia bekerja sebagai eksekutif kunci.
[laughter]
[tertawa]
(Voice) Jeong So-ram quit here.
(Suara) Jeong So-ram berhenti di sini.
I just ended up with a scammer.
Saya baru saja berakhir dengan penipu.
[Vocal cord clicks tongue]
[Pita suara mendecakkan lidah]
(Jonghoon) Rep. Let's check this out
(Jonghoon) Perwakilan. Mari kita periksa ini
What is it?
Apa itu?
(Jong Hoon) This is Jeong So-ram’s call log.
(Jong Hoon) Ini adalah log panggilan Jeong So-ram.
I have a record of my phone call with the congressman.
Saya punya catatan panggilan telepon saya dengan anggota kongres.
[Strengthening] Oh, can’t that be true?
[Penguatan] Oh, bukankah itu benar?
No, well, here and
Tidak, baiklah, ini dia
(Jonghoon) If you look behind here, A call I had a few days ago...
(Jonghoon) Jika Anda melihat ke belakang sini, Sebuah panggilan yang saya terima beberapa hari yang lalu...
(Vocal cords) [in an exasperated voice] Hey
(Pita suara) [dengan suara jengkel] Hei
What are you doing now?
Apa yang kamu lakukan sekarang?
yes?
Ya?
(Vocal cords) It’s quite unpleasant.
(Pita suara) Cukup tidak menyenangkan.
What do Jeong So-ram and I do? Are you saying it could be an affair?
Apa yang saya dan Jeong So-ram lakukan? Maksudmu itu mungkin perselingkuhan?
No, well, I don't mean that at all.
Tidak, aku tidak bermaksud seperti itu sama sekali.
Ha, I even pulled up the call history. It's obvious when you see it coming
Ha, aku bahkan membuka riwayat panggilannya. Sudah jelas ketika Anda melihatnya datang
(vocal cord) Very unpleasant
(pita suara) Sangat tidak menyenangkan
Let's go out
Ayo keluar
(Jonghoon) Oh, we’re just talking about the congressman.
(Jonghoon) Oh, kita hanya berbicara tentang anggota kongres.
Is it possible for Ms. Jeong So-ram? I wonder if you know my whereabouts...
Apakah mungkin untuk Nona Jeong So-ram? Aku ingin tahu apakah kamu tahu keberadaanku...
I don't know
Saya tidak tahu
(Voice) Jeong So-ram and I Don't think about getting involved.
(Suara) Jeong So-ram dan aku Jangan berpikir untuk terlibat.
If something like this comes back to me I won't stay still
Jika hal seperti ini kembali padaku Saya tidak akan tinggal diam
[dark music]
[musik gelap]
[Cracking sound]
[Suara retak]
(Youngjin) With Jeong So-ram I guess you talk on the phone often.
(Youngjin) Dengan Jeong So-ram Saya kira Anda sering berbicara di telepon.
(Voice) About the ban keep talking
(Suara) Tentang larangan itu terus berbicara
[Youngjin’s light sigh]
[Desah ringan Youngjin]
(Youngjin) And that Jeong So-ram That Noh Sang-cheon relationship is an internal affair.
(Youngjin) Dan Jeong So-ram itu Hubungan Noh Sang-cheon adalah urusan internal.
(Vocal cords) Okay, if you’re going to say something pointless.
(Pita suara) Oke, jika Anda ingin mengatakan sesuatu yang tidak ada gunanya.
I used it for money laundering.
Saya menggunakannya untuk pencucian uang.
(Youngjin) Use it for semiconductor manufacturing.
(Youngjin) Gunakan untuk pembuatan semikonduktor.
Gold allowed without customs duties Pull it back
Emas diperbolehkan tanpa bea masuk Tarik kembali
It was used for money laundering.
Itu digunakan untuk pencucian uang.
[Strengthening] No Sang-cheon
[Penguatan] Tidak ada Sang-cheon
How do you know that?
Bagaimana kamu tahu itu?
I saw that scene once I've followed you before
Saya melihat adegan itu sekali Aku sudah mengikutimu sebelumnya
[rattling sound]
[suara berderak]
(Youngjin) He took me with him when he came. When I go, I go alone.
(Youngjin) Dia membawaku bersamanya ketika dia datang. Ketika saya pergi, saya pergi sendiri.
This fucking guy
Pria sialan ini
So?
Jadi?
Let's take that gold?
Mari kita ambil emas itu?
(Youngjin) IC
(Youngjin) IC
You can't do it if you stow away.
Anda tidak dapat melakukannya jika Anda bersembunyi.
So we have to move quickly.
Jadi kita harus bergerak cepat.
(Vocal chords) But that’s right
(Akord vokal) Tapi itu benar
Talk like that
Bicara seperti itu
Why are you doing this to me?
Mengapa kamu melakukan ini padaku?
Ugh, use it for political funding.
Ugh, gunakan untuk pendanaan politik.
To play kingmaker Above all, you need money
Untuk bermain sebagai raja Yang terpenting, Anda membutuhkan uang
Damn it
Sialan
[Sound of vocal cords straining] [Youngjin moans in pain]
[Suara pita suara tegang] [Youngjin mengerang kesakitan]
(Voice chords) You stabbed Noh Sang-cheon at the police. [nervous music]
(Voice chord) Anda menikam Noh Sang-cheon ke arah polisi. [musik gugup]
Do you think I don’t know?
Apakah kamu pikir aku tidak tahu?
What is the real reason you came to see me? You cheater!
Apa alasan sebenarnya kamu datang menemuiku? Kamu penipu!
What kind of scam are you trying to do?
Penipuan macam apa yang Anda coba lakukan?
(Youngjin) Hey, you fucking bastard! [성대의 당황한 소리]
(Youngjin) Hei, bajingan sialan! [성대의 당황한 소리]
더 때려 봐, 더, 이 개새끼야!
더 때려 봐, 더, 이 개새끼야!
Fuck you!
Persetan denganmu!
우리 둘 다 오늘 좆 되는 거야
Bagaimana Cara Mendapatkan Uang Kembali
- (영진) 이 씹새끼야 - 그거 안 치워?
- (영진) 이 씹새끼야 - 그거 안 치워?
(Youngjin) If No Sang-cheon gets caught, You can eat forbidden food
(Youngjin) Jika No Sang-cheon tertangkap, Anda bisa makan makanan terlarang
It's perfect for political funding!
Ini sempurna untuk pendanaan politik!
어차피 검은돈인데, 이 개새끼야!
어차피 검은돈인데, 이 개새끼야!
[영진이 씩씩거린다] [문이 탁 열린다]
[영진이 씩씩거린다] [문이 탁 열린다]
[광신의 놀란 소리]
[광신의 놀란소리]
씨발
itu
괜히 왔네, 씨
괜히 왔네, 씨
[영진의 거친 숨소리]
[영진의 거친 숨소리]
[거친 숨소리]
[거친 숨소리]
맷값이나 줘, 이씨
맷값이나 줘, 이씨
씨발, 존나 짜네, 씹새끼, 씨
씨발, 존나 짜네, 씹새끼, 씨
씨발 새끼, 진짜
씨발 새끼, 진짜
[무거운 음악]
[무거운 음악]
(병준) 나는 4억이야, 자그마치
(병준) 나는 4억이야, 자그마치
귀신한테 홀렸는지 집까지 대출받아 넣었는데
귀신한테 홀렸는지 Panduan Bisnis Lainnya
[떨리는 숨소리]
[떨리는 숨소리]
꼭 찾아야 돼, 꼭
꼭 찾아야 돼, 꼭
그 돈 있어야
그돈 있어야
흩어진 우리 가족 다시 합칠 수 있어
Bagaimana Cara Mendapatkan Uang Kembali
(소람) 어쩌겠어요
(소람) 어쩌겠어요
주어진 운명대로 사셔야죠
Layanan Manajemen Keuangan
[휴대전화 진동음]
[휴대전화 진동음]
(성대) 노상천 옆에 잘 붙어 있어?
(성대) 노상천 옆에 잘 붙어 있어?
(Soram) Didn’t you hear what I said?
(Soram) Apakah kamu tidak mendengar apa yang saya katakan?
I'm at the victim's office.
Saya di kantor korban.
(Vocal cords) Why there?
(Pita suara) Kenapa disana?
(Soram) Go and spend some time Please hold on...
(Soram) Pergi dan luangkan waktu Tolong tunggu...
[Meaningful music] But, when I think about it,
[Musik yang bermakna] Tapi, ketika aku memikirkannya,
Chairman Roh took me away I think he's trying to move
Ketua Roh membawaku pergi Saya pikir dia mencoba untuk bergerak
(Soram) I think Song Youngjin is dead too. The reason is not clear
(Soram) Menurutku Song Youngjin juga sudah mati. Alasannya tidak jelas
What should I say, in the tiger’s den?
Apa yang harus kukatakan, di sarang harimau?
Does it feel like you were thrown in as prey?
Apakah Anda merasa seperti dilempar sebagai mangsa?
Secretary Jeong, you are not rusty.
Sekretaris Jeong, kamu tidak berkarat.
It's the same skill as hitting me in the back.
Itu sama saja dengan memukulku dari belakang.
That's an old story.
Itu cerita lama.
(Soram) I apologized
(Soram) Saya minta maaf
(Vocal chords) Anyway, Noh Sang-cheon I'm organizing it one by one
(Akord vokal) Pokoknya, Noh Sang-cheon Saya mengaturnya satu per satu
people who know their secrets
orang yang mengetahui rahasianya
How did you know?
Bagaimana kamu tahu?
Song Young-jin is that bastard, that I'm alive and well
Song Young-jin adalah bajingan itu Saya masih hidup dan sehat
(Soram) [surprised] Really?
(Soram) [terkejut] Benarkah?
Are you alive?
Apakah kamu masih hidup?
(Vocal cords) Yes, I was here.
(Pita suara) Ya, saya tadi di sini.
I feel like I have a sore leg
Aku merasa kakiku sakit
I'll call Noh Sang-cheon.
Saya akan menelepon Noh Sang-cheon.
It's right next to it no matter what happens
Itu tepat di sebelahnya tidak peduli apa yang terjadi
I'm going to China this time I might never come back
Saya akan ke China kali ini Saya mungkin tidak akan pernah kembali
I
saya
Can we get back on track?
Bisakah kita kembali ke jalur yang benar?
(Vocal cords) What's so important about that?
(Pita suara) Apa pentingnya hal itu?
There must be something more important than that.
Pasti ada sesuatu yang lebih penting dari itu.
Secretary Jeong
Sekretaris Jeong
I will make you think of me as your benefactor for the rest of your life.
Saya akan membuat Anda menganggap saya sebagai dermawan Anda selama sisa hidup Anda.
Do your best
Lakukan yang terbaik
[Call end sound]
[Suara akhir panggilan]
[heavy music]
[musik berat]
These are having fun
Ini sedang bersenang-senang
[snort]
[mendengus]
Um...
eh...
(Attendant) Chairman He told me to bring him with me.
(Petugas) Ketua Dia menyuruhku untuk membawanya bersamaku.
Let’s pack our bags.
Ayo kemasi tas kita.
What burden do I have?
Beban apa yang saya punya?
[Door paper rattles]
[Kertas pintu bergetar]
(Byungjun) Where are you going? I bought some snacks
(Byungjun) Mau kemana? Saya membeli beberapa makanan ringan
Who is it? Where do you think you've seen it?
Siapa itu? Menurut Anda, di mana Anda pernah melihatnya?
I'm an acquaintance
Saya seorang kenalan
I'll go out for a moment and come back
Aku akan keluar sebentar dan kembali
(affectionately) Wait a minute
(dengan sayang) Tunggu sebentar
What's strange?
Apa yang aneh?
(Byungjun) I thought of this person
(Byungjun) Saya memikirkan orang ini
He's the guy next to Noh Sang-cheon. Bodyguard, something like that!
Dia pria di sebelah Noh Sang-cheon. Pengawal, sesuatu seperti itu!
(affectionately) What?
(dengan penuh kasih sayang) Apa?
Hey, bitch!
Hei, jalang!
You're on the road Are you still in touch?
Anda sedang dalam perjalanan Apakah Anda masih berhubungan?
why are you here Are you here to steal some information?
kenapa kamu di sini Apakah Anda di sini untuk mencuri informasi?
[Dajeong’s surprised exclamation] (Attendant) Are you leaving first?
[Seruan terkejut Dajeong] (Petugas) Apakah Anda berangkat dulu?
[Soram’s trembling breathing]
[Nafas Soram yang gemetar]
(Sweet) [Strongly] Where are we going? You bitch!
(Manis) [Sangat] Kemana kita akan pergi? Dasar jalang!
- (affectionately) Huh? where are you going - (Byungjun) Oh, wait, wait, wait
- (dengan penuh kasih sayang) Hah? kemana kamu pergi - (Byungjun) Oh, tunggu, tunggu, tunggu
(affectionately) Oh my! [Da-jeong’s embarrassed voice]
(dengan penuh kasih sayang) Ya ampun! [Suara malu Da-jeong]
Oh my! oh my!
Ya ampun! ya ampun!
(Byungjun) No, this person is now!
(Byungjun) Tidak, orang ini sekarang!
[Byungjun’s groans in pain] [Da-jeong’s labored moans]
[Byungjun mengerang kesakitan] [erangan keras Da-jeong]
(affectionately) Hey, you bastard Hey, you bastard!
(dengan penuh kasih sayang) Hei, bajingan Hei, kamu bajingan!
hey!
Hai!
[Sound of encouragement from attendant] [Da-jeong’s moans of pain]
[Suara dorongan dari petugas] [erangan kesakitan Da-jeong]
(Byungjun) Hey, where are you going!
(Byungjun) Hei, kamu mau kemana!
[Byung-jun’s groans of difficulty]
[erangan kesulitan Byung-jun]
[Dajeong cries]
[Dajeong menangis]
Hey, hey, you bitch...
Hei, hei, kamu jalang...
[Da-jeong’s labored moans]
[erangan keras Da-jeong]
[Byung-jun’s groans of difficulty]
[erangan kesulitan Byung-jun]
[Soram’s frightened breathing] [Byungjun’s moans]
[Nafas Soram yang ketakutan] [erangan Byungjun]
[Byungjun’s groans in pain]
[Byungjun mengerang kesakitan]
(affectionately) Hey!
(dengan penuh kasih sayang) Hei!
Hey, you bastard!
Hei, kamu bajingan!
[Sustaining moans]
[Menahan erangan]
[Da-jeong’s moans of pain]
[erangan kesakitan Da-jeong]
[Rough breathing]
[Nafas kasar]
(Jae Hwang) Huh? Where are you going?
(Jae Hwang) Hah? Kemana kamu pergi?
Byeongjun, give me something to eat. They said they bought it
Byeongjun, beri aku sesuatu untuk dimakan. Mereka bilang mereka membelinya
[Byungjun’s scream] [Clicking sound]
[Teriakan Byungjun] [Suara klik]
What are you talking about?
Apa yang kamu bicarakan?
It sounds like Mr. Byeongjun’s voice.
Kedengarannya seperti suara Tuan Byeongjun.
[Soram’s heavy breathing]
[Nafas Soram yang berat]
[Da-jeong and Byeong-jun’s groans of difficulty] (Byungjun) Stop
[Erangan kesulitan Da-jeong dan Byeong-jun] (Byungjun) Berhenti
(affectionately) No! No, this...
(dengan penuh kasih sayang) Tidak! Tidak, ini...
[Sound of encouragement from attendant] [Byungjun’s groans in pain]
[Suara dorongan dari petugas] [Byungjun mengerang kesakitan]
What are you!
Apa kamu!
[Sound of encouragement from attendant]
[Suara dorongan dari petugas]
[Jaehwang groans in pain]
[Jaehwang mengerang kesakitan]
(Byungjun) Stop it, you bastard!
(Byungjun) Hentikan, bajingan!
[수행원의 힘주는 숨소리]
[수행원의 힘주는 숨소리]
[병준의 아파하는 신음]
[병준의 아파하는 신음]
(다정) 이 개새끼야!
(다정) 이 개새끼야!
You fucking bastard, why are you hitting me?
Dasar bajingan, kenapa kamu memukulku?
[Sound of surprise]
[Suara kejutan]
[Dark sound effect]
[Efek suara gelap]
[groans with difficulty]
[mengerang dengan susah payah]
[surprised gasp]
[terkejut terkesiap]
[Byung-jun’s groans of difficulty]
[erangan kesulitan Byung-jun]
[Moaning in pain] [nervous music]
[Mengerang kesakitan] [musik gugup]
[The spirit of the Emperor]
[Semangat Kaisar]
[Jaehwang’s labored breathing]
[Nafas Jaehwang yang sesak]
[Dark sound effect]
[Efek suara gelap]
[groans with difficulty]
[mengerang dengan susah payah]
[Byungjun’s groans in pain]
[Byungjun mengerang kesakitan]
[Jaehwang’s heavy breathing]
[Nafas Jaehwang yang berat]
[Sound of evil]
[Suara jahat]
[Jaehwang’s encouraging sound] [Embarrassed sounds from attendant]
[Suara Jaehwang yang menyemangati] [Suara malu dari petugas]
[Attendant’s groans of difficulty] [Jaehwang’s embarrassed breathing]
[Erangan kesulitan petugas] [Nafas Jaehwang yang malu]
[Sound of surprise] [The knife falls down]
[Suara kejutan] [Pisaunya jatuh]
[Heavy breathing]
[Nafas berat]
[Sound of surprise]
[Suara kejutan]
[Jaehwang’s heavy breathing]
[Nafas Jaehwang yang berat]
[Attendant’s groans of difficulty] [Da-jeong’s scared voice]
[Erangan kesulitan petugas] [Suara ketakutan Da-jeong]
[bang]
[bang]
[siren sound]
[suara sirene]
[Knocking sound] [The door clicks open]
[Suara ketukan] [Pintunya terbuka]
You found it?
Anda menemukannya?
(Jonghoon) Investigation result report
(Jonghoon) Laporan hasil investigasi
Submission postponed?
Pengiriman ditunda?
(Dohan) Yes, there are contradictions in the investigation and There are some parts that are lacking
(Dohan) Ya, ada kontradiksi dalam penyelidikan dan Ada beberapa bagian yang kurang
Check it out some more I decided to write
Coba lihat lagi Saya memutuskan untuk menulis
Due to the death of the suspect Wasn’t the internal investigation concluded?
Akibat meninggalnya tersangka Bukankah penyelidikan internal sudah selesai?
When writing a report on the results of an investigation You know the basic principles, right?
Saat menulis laporan hasil penyelidikan Anda tahu prinsip dasarnya, bukan?
Are you asking because I think you don’t know?
Apakah Anda bertanya karena saya pikir Anda tidak tahu?
'Are there any contradictions in the investigation records?'
'Apakah ada kontradiksi dalam catatan investigasi?'
There is
Ada
(Dohan) ‘Investigation is insufficient’
(Dohan) 'Investigasi tidak cukup'
'In other words, was there anything that needed further investigation?'
'Dengan kata lain, apakah ada sesuatu yang perlu diselidiki lebih lanjut?'
There is
Ada
‘Contents of various decrees’
‘Isi berbagai keputusan’
'For the purpose of the investigation 'Is it faithfully written?'
'Untuk tujuan penyelidikan 'Apakah ini ditulis dengan setia?'
Yes, faithfully to its purpose. It was about to be written
Ya, setia pada tujuannya. Itu akan segera ditulis
Jeong Jae-hwang confirmed as the culprit
Jeong Jae-hwang membenarkan sebagai pelakunya
speed up the case For the purpose of finishing
mempercepat kasus ini Untuk keperluan finishing
Please check.
Silakan periksa.
Where was Jeong Jae-hwang kidnapped?
Di mana Jeong Jae-hwang diculik?
Check the CCTV I will write a report on the results of the investigation.
Periksa CCTV-nya Saya akan menulis laporan tentang hasil penyelidikan.
[Meaningful music]
[Musik yang bermakna]
What is your current position as a detective?
Apa posisi Anda saat ini sebagai detektif?
Why did it change in just a few days?
Mengapa itu berubah hanya dalam beberapa hari?
People change depending on the situation
Orang berubah tergantung situasinya
The conductor remains unchanged. Were you a consistent person?
Konduktornya tetap tidak berubah. Apakah Anda orang yang konsisten?
(Nayeon) Sincerity also depends on the situation That it can change at any time
(Nayeon) Ketulusan juga tergantung situasi Bahwa hal itu bisa berubah sewaktu-waktu
Now that I'm an adult, I understand.
Sekarang aku sudah dewasa, aku mengerti.
So even now I don’t want to blame the conductor.
Begitu pun sekarang Saya tidak ingin menyalahkan kondektur.
(Nayeon) That’s probably the situation.
(Nayeon) Mungkin itulah situasinya.
I made a mistake
Saya membuat kesalahan
I wasn't leaving this case to you.
Aku tidak akan menyerahkan kasus ini padamu.
(Detective Park) So, you are the suspect. Evidence that Jeong Jae-hwang did it
(Detektif Park) Jadi, Anda adalah tersangkanya. Bukti bahwa Jeong Jae-hwang yang melakukannya
Let's check as much as we can, okay?
Mari kita periksa sebanyak yang kita bisa, oke?
(Dohan) Deputy Director’s movements on the day he was kidnapped
(Dohan) Pergerakan Wakil Direktur pada hari dia diculik
Can’t you check it through call records?
Tidak bisakah Anda memeriksanya melalui catatan panggilan?
The location of the call was provided
Lokasi panggilan telah disediakan
(Dohan) Secure all nearby CCTVs
(Dohan) Amankan semua CCTV terdekat
It's late, but let's check for sure.
Sudah terlambat, tapi mari kita periksa pastinya.
During the last three murders
Selama tiga pembunuhan terakhir
If Jeong Jae-hwang can get the copper wire, he will get it.
Jika Jeong Jae-hwang bisa mendapatkan kawat tembaga itu, dia akan mendapatkannya.
(Detective Park) Yes, ugh.
(Detektif Park) Ya, ugh.
I finally pooped and didn’t wipe it. The uncomfortable feeling will go away.
Saya akhirnya buang air besar dan tidak menghapusnya. Perasaan tidak nyaman akan hilang.
I feel bad while eating. Is that really true? Senior, really
Saya merasa tidak enak saat makan. Apakah itu benar? Senior, sungguh
[Detective Park is babbling]
[Detektif Park mengoceh]
[Detective Shin’s annoyed voice]
[Suara kesal Detektif Shin]
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
[Suara langkah kaki mendekat]
(Audit Manager) Oh, you’re eating.
(Manajer Audit) Oh, Anda sedang makan.
How are you? Our old team leader? [The door slams shut]
Apa kabarmu? Pemimpin tim lama kita? [Pintu dibanting hingga tertutup]
What's going on?
Apa yang terjadi?
(Audit Manager) Oh, well, it’s nothing special.
(Manajer Audit) Oh ya, tidak ada yang istimewa.
Because of the former team leader’s last disciplinary action.
Karena tindakan disiplin terakhir mantan ketua tim tersebut.
The punishment hasn't even ended Because someone lets them go as they please
Hukumannya bahkan belum berakhir Karena seseorang membiarkan mereka pergi sesuka hatinya
That's illegal because it ignores procedures.
Itu ilegal karena mengabaikan prosedur.
[Dohan’s exasperated voice] Even if I want to overlook this
[Suara jengkel Dohan] Meski aku ingin mengabaikannya
There is an audit scheduled soon.
Ada jadwal audit segera.
So
Jadi
So what do you say?
Jadi apa yang kamu katakan?
[The inspector general laughs]
[Inspektur Jenderal tertawa]
(Audit Manager) Let’s go home, right now.
(Manajer Audit) Ayo pulang sekarang juga.
[Detective Park’s angry breathing]
[Napas marah Detektif Park]
[Detective Shin’s absurd remarks] [dark music]
[Pernyataan Detektif Shin yang tidak masuk akal] [musik gelap]
[Moon So-ri]
[Bulan So-ri]
[Each cell phone rings]
[Setiap ponsel berdering]
[Everyone is surprised]
[Semua orang terkejut]
(Woman 7) Oh, how did this happen?
(Wanita 7) Oh, bagaimana ini bisa terjadi?
(Yeon-Gwang) Ah, why is this, oh [Cheongju’s embarrassed voice]
(Yeon-Gwang) Ah, kenapa begini, oh [Suara malu Cheongju]
(Cheongju’s house) What is this?
(Rumah Cheongju) Apa ini?
Why is this, this coming again?
Mengapa ini terjadi lagi?
(Reunion) Jaehwang?
(Reuni) Jaehwang?
[nervous music]
[musik gugup]
Jaehwang is dead.
Jaehwang sudah mati.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[suara ponsel bergetar]
[tire rubbing sound]
[suara gesekan ban]
- Yes - (Reunion) I got a text message again.
- Iya - (Reuni) Saya mendapat pesan teks lagi.
It came to me too
Itu juga datang kepadaku
(Reunion) Isn’t Jaehwang alive?
(Reuni) Bukankah Jaehwang masih hidup?
Nayeon, you confirmed it. Jaehwang is dead
Nayeon, kamu sudah memastikannya. Jaehwang sudah mati
Are you sure you saw it?
Apakah Anda yakin Anda melihatnya?
That's right
Itu benar
(Reunion) Then who is this?
(Reuni) Lalu siapa ini?
You'll find out when you go.
Anda akan mengetahuinya ketika Anda pergi.
[Call end sound] (Yeon-Gwang) What are you saying?
[Suara akhir panggilan] (Yeon-Gwang) Apa yang kamu katakan?
[Nervous breathing]
[Nafas gugup]
[tire rubbing sound]
[suara gesekan ban]
[hissing sound]
[suara mendesis]
[Knocking on car window] Over there.
[Mengetuk jendela mobil] Di sana.
(Jonghun) Are you okay? Hey there
(Jonghun) Apakah kamu baik-baik saja? Hai
[Ringles the handle]
[Membunyikan pegangannya]
[Sound of knocking on car window] [Oncoming car engine sound]
[Suara ketukan di jendela mobil] [Suara mesin mobil datang]
Hey there
Hai
Hey, are you okay?
Hei, kamu baik-baik saja?
[Heavy sound effect] I was waiting, you bastard.
[Efek suara berat] Aku sedang menunggu, bajingan.
Take off your mask
Buka topengmu
Take it off quickly!
Lepaskan dengan cepat!
Before peeling off the skin on my face
Sebelum mengelupas kulit wajahku
[Tense sound effect]
[Efek suara menegangkan]
[Dark sound effect] [Jonghun’s surprised gasp]
[Efek suara gelap] [Jonghun terkesiap kaget]
[Meaningful music]
[Musik yang bermakna]
[Calm music]
[Musik yang tenang]
Subtitle: Ahn Hyo-mi
Subjudul: Ahn Hyo-mi